newunblocker.com 2016-11-24

# New Unblocker - Privacy Policy

##  » Privacy Policy - NewUnblocker.com

### Introduction

Thank you for taking the time to review our Privacy Policy. We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our web site NewUnblocker.com. This document discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices we maintain at our web site.

At times, NewUnblocker.com henceforth referred to as New Unblocker/We will collect certain personal information about visitors who access our web site. Such information will include non-identifiable personal information. Non-identifiable information is gathered automatically when you visit our web site or those web sites accessed through us, and stored for use in our system. Except where the law requires otherwise, we undertake to protect the confidentiality of such data. In most cases, we collect this information to ensure network integrity and that we continue to provide you with the most relevant content and best possible service that suits your needs. In some cases, we are required by law to collect personal information about users.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain to users what types of information we will collect and how that information is used.

### Confidentiality

User privacy is something we take very seriously at New Unblocker. We do not provide, sell, rent, or lease (except where required by law) the personal information of our users to any parties outside of New Unblocker. We undertake not to sell your personal information to third parties for commercial or marketing purposes. We use collected information for statistical purposes, to administer our systems, and to provide technical support.

We undertake to protect the confidentiality of our customers and users. New Unblocker respects customer privacy and the privacy of those accessing our web site or those web sites accessed through us.

### Collection of Personal Data

We collect personal information from you (through the use of cookie technology) when you access our web site or web sites accessed through us, including the URL from which you linked into our web site, your IP address, and your browser type and version, all of which are collected in an anonymous manner without being linked to any of your personal information.

#### Log Files

Like many other web sites, New Unblocker makes use of log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type & version information, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This data however will not be used to identify individual users who will at all times remain anonymous. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. New Unblocker does use cookies to store information about our visitorâ€™s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web page content based on visitor's browser type or other information that the visitor sends via his/her browser.

More about http cookies - <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie>

### Use of Personal Data

New Unblocker may collect and share aggregated user data with business partners, sponsors or other third parties for the purposes of developing content and ensuring relevant advertising and content, such user data will never be used to identify individual users. These business partners and affiliated companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

Any information New Unblocker collects from you through correspondence with us, whether via email, by telephone or by written letter, will only be used to address matters within that correspondence. If this requires referring such correspondence within New Unblocker or to a third party to ensure customer service, your personal information will only be disclosed to the point necessary to address your query or concerns, and will otherwise be kept confidential.

### Advertisers

We use outside advertising companies to display advertisements on our web site. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and/or web beacons on our site, to collect data in the advertisement serving process. Our advertising partners include Google AdSense (<https://www.google.com/adsense/>), AdBrite ([http://www.adbrite.com](http://www.adbrite.com/)) and CPALead, LLC ([http://www.cpalead.com](http://www.cpalead.com/)).

These third party advertisement servers or advertisement networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on NewUnblocker.com. They automatically receive your Internet Protocol (IP) address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party advertisement networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Please note that New Unblocker has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third party advertisers, once they are granted permission to use cookies for advertising within our web site.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third party advertisement servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Please check our advertisersâ€™ web sites for respective privacy policies;

  * Google's Privacy Policy which applies to all of the products, services, and web sites offered by Google - <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>
  * AdBrite's Privacy Policy - <http://www.adbrite.com/mb/privacy.php>
  * CPALead, LLC's Privacy Policy - <http://www.cpalead.com/privacy.php>

#### Google advertising and DoubleClick DART cookies for Interest based advertising

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visited websites. We may use DART cookies for ad serving through Googleâ€™s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a website using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The DART cookie does NOT gather personal information but the browsing history in order to support Googleâ€™s Interest based advertising. The ads served will be targeted based on your previous online browsing history.

More information on the DoubleClick DART cookie which is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads can be found at <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx>

You can opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy found at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> or DART Ad-Serving and Search Cookie Opt-Out page at <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

If you wish to disable cookies selectively or entirely, you may do so through your individual browser options or using special software. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective web sites. Alternatively you can use the guide at <http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1>

### Public Space (Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms and Third Party Web Sites)

Any information that users disclose in a public space, including on any bulletin board, chat room or any site accessed through New Unblocker, is available to anyone else who visits that space. New Unblocker cannot safeguard any information you disclose there & hence cannot be held responsible.

### Email Subscriptions

If a user wishes to subscribe to our user group (powered by Yahoo Groups), we ask for contact information such as email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. You can access Yahoo Privacy Policy governing Yahoo Groups at <http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/>

### Site Linking

Our web site contains many links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to us. New Unblocker cannot protect any information you may disclose on these sites and recommends that you review the relevant privacy policy statements of those sites you visit. New Unblocker cannot be held responsible for any use of your personal information arising from you disclosing personal information on third party sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

### General

New Unblocker reserves the right to disclose information about users where required in good faith, to do so by law or to exercise our legal rights or defend ourselves against legal claims.

New Unblocker reserves our rights to disclose your personal information where you have given us explicit legal written consent to do so.

New Unblocker further reserves the right to share information with law enforcement to investigate or prevent illegal activities being committed over our network.

New Unblocker reserves the right to monitor user and network traffic for site security purposes and prevent any unauthorized attempts to tamper with our site or cause damage to our property.

It may be necessary from time to time, to check New Unblocker's privacy policy for changes. New Unblocker reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy or update it without further notification. Customers and site visitors bear the responsibility to ensure that they have read the changes or updates as the case may be.

If you require further information and/or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email using the form available at our web site.

###### Last updated: March 18, 2008.
